A Guide to the Markle Foundation records, Record Group 1-Record Group 3 FA024
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Markle Foundation Administration, 2
  - Markle Foundation Administration - Accession 2, 2; 40.8 Cubic Feet
    - President Lloyd N. Morrisett's Papers, 1927-1992 1965-1992; 1; 24 Cubic Feet 20 boxes
      - Professional Activities, 1960-1994; 3
        This subseries reflects Morrisett's attendance at workshops, institutes, and seminars, as well as his participation in numerous organizations. Included are speeches, writings, and testimony on a wide area of topics including higher education, communication and public policy, public broadcasting, educational television, cable television, foundations, and major trends and issues affecting America. Additional materials include correspondence, memoranda and attachments, minutes, financial data, and printed materials.
        - Committees - John W. Gardner Public Service Award Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 645)
        - Committees - John W. Gardner Public Service Award Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 646)
        - Committees - John W. Gardner Public Service Award Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 647)
        - Committees - Municipal Broadcasting System Task Force, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 648)
        - Committees - Municipal Broadcasting System Task Force, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 649)
        - Committees - Municipal Broadcasting System Task Force, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 650)
        - Committees - "Prospects For Mankind" Advisory Board - Hudson Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 651)
        - Committees - "Prospects For Mankind" Advisory Board - Hudson Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 652)
        - Committees - Teleprompter Program Advisory Board, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 653)
        - Committees - Teleprompter Program Advisory Board, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 654)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 655)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 656)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 657)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 658)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 659)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 660)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 661)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 662)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 663)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 664)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 665)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 666)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 667)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 668)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 669)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 670)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 671)
        - Meetings and Speeches, 1960-1962, 1964-1966, 1969, 1971-1980, 1983-1986, 1992, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 672)
        - Memberships and Associations - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1970-1972, 1975-1976, 1988, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 673)
        - Memberships and Associations - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Investment and Finance Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 674)
        - Memberships and Associations - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Investment and Finance Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 675)
        - Memberships and Associations - Century Association, 1988-1991 (Box 18, Folder 676)
        - Memberships and Associations - Cleveland Conference, 1980-1988 (Box 18, Folder 677)
        - Memberships and Associations - Council On Foreign Relations, 1977, 1981-1991 (Box 18, Folder 678)
        - Memberships and Associations - Council On Foreign Relations, 1977, 1981-1991 (Box 18, Folder 679)
        - Memberships and Associations - Council On Foreign Relations - Membership Task Force On Women, 1988-1991 (Box 18, Folder 680)
        - Memberships and Associations - Gannet Center For Media Studies, 1985-1991 (Box 18, Folder 681)
        - Memberships and Associations - Haskins Laboratory - Annual Meeting, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 682)
        - Memberships and Associations - Haskins Laboratory - Annual Meeting, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 683)
        - Memberships and Associations - Haskins Laboratory - Administrative Committee, 1982-1983, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 684)
        - Memberships and Associations - Haskins Laboratory - Correspondence, 1983-1991 (Box 19, Folder 685)
        - Memberships and Associations - Haskins Laboratory - Correspondence, 1983-1991 (Box 19, Folder 686)
        - Memberships and Associations - Haskins Laboratory - Investment and Finance Committee, 1983-1986, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 687)
        - Memberships and Associations - Haskins Laboratory - University Affiliations, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 688)
        - Memberships and Associations - National Geographic Society Education Foundation, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 689)
        - Memberships and Associations - National Geographic Society Education Foundation, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 690)
        - Memberships and Associations - New York Academy of Sciences - Board of Governors Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 691)
        - Memberships and Associations - New York Academy of Sciences - Board of Governors Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 692)
        - Memberships and Associations - New York Academy of Sciences - Board of Governors Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 693)
        - Memberships and Associations - New York Academy of Sciences - Board of Governors Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 694)
        - Memberships and Associations - New York Academy of Sciences - Board of Governors Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 695)
        - Memberships and Associations - New York Academy of Sciences - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 19, Folder 696)
        - Memberships and Associations - New York Academy of Sciences - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 19, Folder 697)
        - Memberships and Associations - New York Academy of Sciences - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 19, Folder 698)
        - Memberships and Associations - New York Academy of Sciences - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 19, Folder 699)
        - Memberships and Associations - New York World Television Festival - Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 700)
        - Memberships and Associations - Television Audience Assessment Inc. - Board of Directors, 1980-1985 (Box 19, Folder 701)
        - Miscellany - Correspondence, 1963, 1966-1967, 1974, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 702)
        - Miscellany - Interview on Children's Television Workshop (CTW) by Student, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 703)
        - Miscellany - Shiller Seminar, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 704)
        - Oral History Transcript, Part I, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 705)
        - Oral History Transcript, Part II, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 706)
        - Testimony, 1971, 1973-1974, 1977, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 707)
        - Writings - Articles (Reprints), 1959, 1961, 1964-1967, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 708)
        - Writings - "Children and Television: Lessons From Sesame Street" by Gerald Lesser - Introduction, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 709)
        - Writings - "New York Times" Article, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 710)
        - Writings - "Toward a National Policy for Children's Television - National Commission, International Year of the Child, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 711)
      - Chronological File, 1977-1991; 4
        The subseries includes copies of correspondence and memoranda related to the management and activities of the Markle Foundation, personnel matters, and outside interests.
        - Non-Circulating Blues, 1977-1983 (Box 19, Folder 712)
        - Non-Circulating Blues, 1977-1983 (Box 19, Folder 713)
        - Non-Circulating Blues, 1984-1991 (Box 20, Folder 714)
        - Non-Circulating Blues, 1984-1991 (Box 20, Folder 715)
        - Non-Circulating Blues, 1984-1991 (Box 20, Folder 716)
        - Non-Circulating Blues, 1984-1991 (Box 20, Folder 717)
        - Non-Circulating Blues, 1984-1991 (Box 20, Folder 718)
        - Non-Markle Blues, 1979, 1981-1982, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 719)
        - Non-Markle Blues, 1979, 1981-1982, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 720)
        - Non-Markle Blues, 1979, 1981-1982, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 721)
        - Non-Markle Blues, 1979, 1981-1982, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 722)
        - Non-Markle Blues, 1979, 1981-1982, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 723)
        - Non-Markle Blues, 1979, 1981-1982, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 724)
        - Staff Memoranda, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 725)
      - Personal Files, 1960-1969; 5
        This subseries primarily contains correspondence and materials related to activities prior to Morrisett's position at the Markle Foundation. It also includes congratulatory letters on his new position as president of the Markle Foundation.
        - Congratulatory Letters, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 726)
        - Congratulatory Letters, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 727)
        - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 728)
        - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 729)
        - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 730)
        - Trip to Scotland, England and Denmark, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 731)
    - General Office Files, 1968-1992; 2; 15.6 Cubic Feet 13 boxes
      Subseries 2 - Chronological Files
      - Alphabetical Files, 1
        Subseries 1, Alphabetical Files, includes files identified by individual, organization, or topic. Materials in this subseries consist of memoranda, correspondence, project proposals, records of interviews, reports, printed material, and news releases. The files contain routine as well as unique materials, particularly as they reflect the broad range of interests, activities, and ideas evolving in the field of mass communication and information technology.
        - A, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - A, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
        - A, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        - A, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        - A, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Academic Search Consultation Service, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Academy for Educational Development, 1972, 1975-1978, 1981, 1985, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
        - Administration on Aging, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - Airlie House, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Alerdinck Foundation, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - American Cinemateque - Gene Starvis, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        - American Council of Learned Societies, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        - American Federation of Teachers, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
        - American Institute of Discussion, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - American Museum of the Moving Image, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - American Society of Newspaper Editors, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - American University, 1971, 1973, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - American Video Institute, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - American Women in Radio and Television, Inc. - Phyllis Tritsch, 1981-1982, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - Ameritech, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - ANPA Foundation, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - Appalachian Regional Council, 1971-1972, 1974-1975, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
        - Christopher Arterton - Institute for Citizen Communication, 1986, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
          See also Box 5, Folder 223 - Institute for Democratic Communications.
        - Arts/Video Advisory Service (AVAS) - Laura Lawrence-Dwyer - Arts and Business Council, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
        - Association of Independent Video and Film (FIVF) - Tom Lennon, 1975, 1977, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
        - Astoria Motion Picture and Television Foundation - Richard Kaplan, 1970-1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
        - Atlantic Institute for International Affairs - Judith C. Symonds, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - Atlas World Press - Al Balk, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - B, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - B, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
        - B, 1983-1984, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
        - Bank Street College, 1981-1986, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 32)
        - Bank Street College, 1981-1986, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 33)
        - British Film Institute, 1979, 1981, 1983-1984, 1987-1989, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
        - C, 1971, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
        - C, 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 36)
        - C, 1984, 1987-1988, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 37)
        - California Tomorrow, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 38)
        - Call for Action, 1972, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 39)
        - Carnegie Commission on the Future of Public Broadcasting, 1976, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 40)
        - Carnegie Commission on the Future of Public Broadcasting, 1976, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 41)
        - Carnegie Commission on the Future of Public Broadcasting - Public Radio, May 19, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 42)
        - Carnegie Conference - "Television and Its Educational Potential for Children", 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
        - Carnegie Council on Adolescent Development, May 22, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 44)
        - Carnegie Council on Children, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 45)
        - Carnegie Institute of Washington, 1968-1977, 1979-1980, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 46)
        - Case Western Reserve University, 1970-1971, 1973, 1975, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 47)
        - Bureau of Census, United States Department of Commerce, February 1970 (Box 2, Folder 48)
        - Center for Advanced Study in Behavioral Science, February 23, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 49)
        - Center for the American Woman and Politics - The Eagleton Institute of Politics, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 50)
        - Center for Continuing Education, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 51)
        - Center for Continuing Education, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 52)
        - Center for Continuing Education, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 53)
        - Center for Information on America - Mr. Townsend Scudder, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 54)
        - Center for Investigative Reporting, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 55)
        - Center for Law and Social Policy - Charles R. Halpern, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 56)
        - Center for Social Research, City University of New York (CUNY) - Charles Kadushin, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 57)
        - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions - The Fund for the Republic, Inc., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 58)
        - Center for Study of Responsive Law, 1969, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 59)
        - Center for Understanding Aging - Fran Pratt, Director, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 60)
        - Center for Understanding Media - John Culkin, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 61)
        - Central Educational Network, June 1, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 62)
        - Centre for Mass Communication Research, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 63)
        - Century Association, 1978, 1980-1983, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 64)
        - Century Association, 1978, 1980-1983, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 65)
        - Chicago College of Osteopathic Medicine - Richard W. Languirand, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 66)
        - Chicago Medical School, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 67)
        - Chicago Public Television - Diane Levin, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 68)
        - University of Chicago, 1970-1971, 1973-1976, 1978, 1982-1983, 1986, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 69)
        - University of Chicago - Funding for the Conference on the Preparation for the Study of Medicine, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 70)
        - University of Chicago - Department of Sociology - Terry Clark, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 71)
        - University of Chicago - Peterson Commission, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 72)
        - "Child Development and the Mass Media" - Report of Forum 20 - 1970 White House Conference on Children, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 73)
        - Children and Television, 1968, 1970-1971, 1973-1974, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 74)
        - Children and Television, 1968, 1970-1971, 1973-1974, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 75)
        - Children's Pay Cable Network - Forrest P. Chisman, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 76)
        - Anna Mc G. Chisman - Organization of American States, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 77)
        - Citizen Board of Inquiry, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 78)
        - Citizen Communication Center - Albert H. Kramer, Executive Director, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 79)
        - Citizens Conference on State Legislatures, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 80)
        - Citizens' Research Foundation, 1972-1973, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 81)
        - City of Cincinnati, 1984, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 82)
        - City of Cincinnati - Part I, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 83)
        - City of Cincinnati - Part II, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 84)
        - Coffee House Club, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 85)
        - Commission on Public Broadcasting, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 86)
        - Committee for the Institute of Congress, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 87)
        - Committee for the Study of the American Electorate, 1981, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 88)
          See also Box 4, Folder 197 - Curt Gans.
        - Communication Act Rewrite, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 89)
        - Communication for Change - Scott Jacobs, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 90)
        - Communication Satellite Corporation (COMSAT) - Robert E. Button, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 91)
        - Communications Law Project, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 92)
        - Communications Policy - Background Material, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 93)
        - Communications Policy - Communication Research, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 94)
        - Communications Policy - President's Task Force on Communications Policy - Final Report, August 14, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 95)
        - Communicat Access Television, April 10, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 96)
        - Common Cause, 1970-1971, 1973-1975, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 97)
        - Community Film Workshop Council - Cliff Frazier, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 98)
        - Community News Service - Humberto Cintron, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 99)
        - Community Relations Service - Larry Stils, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 100)
        - Community Research Associates, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 101)
        - Computer Projects - Apple Community Affairs Project - Science Education Department, University of Wisconsin, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 102)
        - University of Connecticut - Health Center, 1968, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 103)
        - Consiglio Italiano per la Science Sociali - Alessandro Silj, 1984, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 104)
        - Constitutional Network, Inc., 1977, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 105)
        - Consumers Union Foundation - Larry Siegel, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 106)
        - Cornell University, 1970-1971, 1973-1976, 1978-1979, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 107)
        - Cornell University - Rose K. Goldsen, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 108)
        - Cornell University - James Teicher, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 109)
        - Corporation For Public Broadcasting, 1969-1978, 1980-1981, 1984, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 110)
        - Corporation For Public Broadcasting, 1969-1978, 1980-1981, 1984, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 111)
        - Corporation For Public Broadcasting - "The Show" - Ward B. Chamberlin, 1969-1970, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 112)
        - Council for the Advancement of Science Writing - Pierre Fraley, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 113)
        - Council for Basic Education, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 114)
        - Council on Children, Media, and Merchandising - Robert Choate, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 115)
        - Council on Children, Media, and Merchandising - Robert Choate, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 116)
        - Council on International and Public Affairs, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 117)
        - Council on Learning, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 118)
        - Bert Cowan, 1970, 1973-1974, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 119)
        - Cecilia Coyle, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 120)
          Hospital nursing home video visits; Carol Hegeman - Foundation for Long Term Care.
        - Lawrence Cranberg, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 121)
          Previous file misplaced.
        - Creighton University, March 5, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 122)
        - Lawrence Cremin, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 123)
        - Cultural Council Foundation, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 124)
        - Michael Dann, May 14, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 125)
        - Donald Dansereau, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 126)
        - E, 1974-1984 (Box 3, Folder 127)
        - Earth Watch, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 128)
        - University of East Anglia - School of Education, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 129)
        - Eastern Educational Television Network, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 130)
        - Economic Development Council, Inc., April 22, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 131)
        - University of Edinburgh, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 132)
        - Education Commission of the States, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 133)
        - Education Development Center - Project I, 1971-1975, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 134)
        - Education Development Center - Project I, 1971-1975, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 135)
        - Education Development Center - "Infinity Factory" Television Series - J. Zacharias, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 136)
        - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Channel 13, 1970, 1972-1977, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 137)
        - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Channel 13 - WNET News Clippings - General, 1971-1972, 1974, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 138)
        - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Channel 13 - WNET News Clippings - Media Reviews, 1971, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 139)
        - Educational Film Library Association - Nadine Convert, March 18, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 140)
        - Educational Products Information Exchange, 1983, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 141)
        - Edward de Bono Foundation - Edward de Bono, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 142)
        - Election Studies, November 1973 (Box 3, Folder 144)
        - Elly Elliot, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 145)
          Former member of "Channels" Board.
        - Emerson College, May 18, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 146)
        - Encyclopaedia Brittannica Education Corporation - William Benton, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 147)
        - Equal Employment Council, Inc. and "Fight Back" - Timothy J. Cooney, February 16, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 148)
        - European North American Committee, September 28, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 149)
        - Harold Evans, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 150)
        - Experimental Television Laboratory - William Watson, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 151)
        - Experiments in Art and Technology, February 22, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 152)
        - Exxon Education Foundation, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 153)
        - Executive Office of the President, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 154)
        - F, 1972-1973, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 155)
        - F, 1979-1984, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 156)
        - Family Communications, Inc. - Music Series for Children, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 157)
        - Foundation For American Communications (FACS), 1982-1983, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 158)
        - Federal Communications Commission, 1970-1971, 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 159)
        - Federal Communications Commission, 1970-1971, 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 160)